

# RENÉ GARCIA

Product Designer

### **PROFILE**

I am a product designer based out of Oakland,CA and specialize in branding and visual identity. My approach is to craft the best creative solutions for the clients business problems through a strategic process. I enjoy creating in a collaborative environment as part of a team as well as taking on projects individually and comfortably.

### CONTACT ME

\_

**\** 707.655.6690

🔀 Designbyrg@gmail.com

# REFERENCES

\_

Rodrigo Resendiz
Graphic Designer/ Tattoo Artist

- **4** 925.337.3795
- Questcreates@gmail.com

#### William Kalolaine

Muralist/Tattoo Artist

- **C** 775.229.3229
- Kalolaine0719@gmail.com

## **EDUCATION**

\_

2018-2019

**BLOC** 

Designer Track Bootcamp

- Design Fundamentals
- Design Foundations
- Front End Foundations

### **EXPERIENCE**

\_

2018-Present

#### LAST ONES COLLECTIVE

Muralist/Designer

- Mural Prepartion & Execution
- Graphic Designer
- Creative Direction
- Create contracts and invoices for clients

2016-2017

#### FIRST AMENDMENT GALLERY

Mural Assistant

- Mural Prepartion & Execution
- Assist In Team Building Workshops
- Shop Employee / Inventory

### SKILLS

\_

**PHOTOSHOP** 

**ILLUSTRATOR** 

**INDESIGN** 

HTML/CSS

RESEARCH

DEVELOPMENT